We call to order the special meeting for the Miami Special Utility Authority Board for Friday, May 27th, 2022.
I pledge allegiance.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America and to the republic for which it stands, one nation, under God, indivisible, with liberty and justice for all.
The meeting will now be continued from the council chambers and reconvene the staff room for the purpose of executive session.
The meeting will now be continued from the staff room and reconvene the council chambers.
Six, resolution 2022-02 of the Board of Trustees of the Miami Special Utility Authority, recommending approval of community financial support and fee waivers to John Vance Auto Group, LLC, related to the development of 521 North Main.
So moved.
Second.
Step.
Aye.
So moved.
Davis.
Aye.
Stain.
Senator.
Aye.
Parker.
And seven, adjournment.
So moved.
Second.
Thank you.